<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fresh look at Self-Hosting on WinterFlow.io</title><link>https://winterflow.io/</link><description>Recent content in Fresh look at Self-Hosting on WinterFlow.io</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://winterflow.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Firecrawl</title><link>https://winterflow.io/catalog/firecrawl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://winterflow.io/catalog/firecrawl/</guid><description>&lt;p>Firecrawl is an API service that takes a URL, crawls it, and converts it into clean markdown or structured data. Firecrawl crawl all accessible subpages and give you clean data for each. No sitemap required.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>LibreChat</title><link>https://winterflow.io/catalog/librechat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://winterflow.io/catalog/librechat/</guid><description>&lt;p>LibreChat is an open-source chat interface that supports multiple AI models and providers, offering a flexible and customizable chat experience.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>n8n</title><link>https://winterflow.io/catalog/n8n/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://winterflow.io/catalog/n8n/</guid><description>&lt;p>n8n is a powerful workflow automation platform that enables you to connect different applications and services together, creating automated workflows without writing code.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>OpenHands AI</title><link>https://winterflow.io/catalog/openhands/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://winterflow.io/catalog/openhands/</guid><description>&lt;p>OpenHands AI is an advanced AI agent designed to assist developers by automating various development tasks. It can perform complex operations like code modification, command execution, web browsing, and even integrate with StackOverflow for code snippets.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://winterflow.io/legal/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://winterflow.io/legal/privacy-policy/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="privacy-policy">Privacy Policy&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Your privacy is important to us. It is WinterFlow&amp;rsquo;s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, winterflow.com, its subdomains, and other sites we own and operate (collectively, the &amp;ldquo;Sites&amp;rdquo;). This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard your information when you visit any of our Sites. Please read this policy carefully to understand our practices regarding your information.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Terms of Service</title><link>https://winterflow.io/legal/terms-of-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://winterflow.io/legal/terms-of-service/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="terms-of-service">Terms of Service&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Welcome to WinterFlow! Please read these Terms of Service (&amp;ldquo;Terms&amp;rdquo;) carefully before using our websites, products, and services (collectively, the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;). By accessing or using the Software, you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you do not agree, please discontinue use of the Software.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="1-acceptance-of-terms">1. Acceptance of Terms&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>By accessing or using WinterFlow, you confirm that you have read, understood, and agree to these Terms, as well as our Privacy Policy.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>